Kids, y'all need to get inside!
The wedding is about to start.
Good afternoon, Ms. Quinn.
I heard Liam's song
on the radio this morning.
Can you believe it? Our very own Liam,
right here in Saint, is on the radio.
I can believe it, Ellen.
Now let's get inside
and watch him marry our Josie.
Yes, ma'am.
Our Liam has quickly become
a bonafide country star.
- Hey, you mind handing those out?
- Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
Good to see you.
Ladies, twelve minutes.
- Oh!
- Twelve minutes, Ms. Quinn?
All the Southern time
in the world, my dear.
I handpicked these this morning
for Josie.
Thank you.
I swear, though,
if one more person
asks me about her groom's
new hit song on the radio...
Ms. Boudreau, I'll be sending
some of the boys
to get you lovely ya-yas
to your seats.
All right.
- Let's put the veil on.
- Okay.
Bethany, isn't she beautiful?
- I love you so much.
- I love you, too.
- Oh, you're gonna make me cry.
- You're gonna make me cry!
Hey, hey, hey,
there's my little sister.
I didn't know you could
clean up like that.
- Oh! Jake!
- Just kidding!
So are you ready for your big brother
to walk you down the aisle?
Is it really time?
It's almost.
Ms. Quinn wants me
to walk Mom down first.
Hey, how you doing?
Are you ready for this?
I'm ready.
Ladies...
Good Lord, don't y'all
look ravishing today.
Oh!
I'm getting married!
Ladies. You guys look beautiful.
- Mason!
- Johnny.
Josie, you look absolutely amazing.
Thank you, Mason.
- Kiera.
- Yeah.
Can me and Johnny talk to you
outside for a minute, please?
Sure. Josie, I'll be right back.
Laura, can you just touch up her lipstick?
Just a little more color.
Absolutely.
Do you think everything's okay?
Oh, yeah, honey,
everything's fine.
This is your special day.
Go like this.
Perfect.
Kiera, what is it?
Is Liam okay?
Liam's fine.
He's fine, he's just...
he's not coming.
I'm sorry, Josie.
What?
We're gonna be here for you.
Yes, we're here for you, honey.
Hell yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
New Orleans, thank you!
Thank you. You guys are awesome.
Now, I'm gonna do one more song
for you all, if that's okay.
I love you, Liam!
Thank you.
Goodnight.
Liam! Liam! Liam!
Liam! Liam!
Liam! Liam! Liam! Liam!
Great, great, great show, man.
You slayed it, as usual.
Vodka. Here we go.
- You see that blonde in the front row?
- Already on it.
Jack's put her in a car
headed to the after party.
I'm not going to the after party, man.
Okay, now, Liam,
the head of the label's gonna be there.
I mean, everyone's real eager to hear
about these new tunes you been working on.
Just have a bottle of vodka
sent up to my room, and a steak.
- All right? I'm starving.
- All right.
Jimmy, he ain't going.
He ain't going.
Ain't nothing like a hometown crowd,
though, right? Am I right?
I'm not from here.
I'm a few towns over.
Not here at all.
All right. Oh.
I'll get your towel, then.
Okay, great.
All right, boys,
good job, good job.
Hey, Liam Page!
I have been trying to get you up
for hours, Liam Page.
Can you stop calling me
"Liam Page"?
You're up! You're up! You're up!
- You're up! You're up! You're up!
- Hey, what are you... That's...
- That's my cell phone.
- Oh, that's a cell phone?
Please, come on...
No, it's broken. You broke it!
Oh, hold on! Wait!
Where are you going, Liam Page?
Oh, my God! Holy!
Okay, well, call me!
Could you please tell me,
where's the nearest cell phone store?
Yes, uh, Mr. Page.
I'd be delighted to assist you.
It's, uh, on the edge of the quarter.
I'd be happy to call you a car.
Can you just tell me how far,
which direction, how many blocks?
Take a right on Royal,
and it's six blocks down on your left.
- Okay.
- Oh, my.
Liam, where are your shoes?
Hey.
I'll give anyone $10,000
if they can fix my phone.
- $10,000.
- Oh, my God...
Mr. Page, uh,
- $10,000. You mind if I...?
- Can you...
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
Well, perhaps, sir,
we can interest you in a newer model?
I don't, I don't want
a newer model, okay?
- I want that... that phone.
- Allow me to assist you, Mr. Page.
- On the house. I'm the store manager.
- Oh.
Jojo?
- Jojo.
- Huh?
Release the device, please.
Thank you.
Why don't you step into my office?
We'll have a little more privacy.
Okay, let's have a look here.
I'll tell you what,
these older boards are tricky.
So, I take it these messages
you need to get to,
they must be very important.
Yes, there's just one.
There's just one.
Just give me one second here.
All right, well it's not gonna
win any beauty contests,
but this should work just fine now.
It's fixed?
I'll give you some privacy
and you can check for yourself.
Okay.
April 9th. One saved message.
Hi, Liam. It's me, Josie.
Country star Liam Page
was spotted earlier today
in the French Quarter.
He was running barefoot,
according to some witnesses.
Doris, hold on. This might be him.
Yep, I got him.
I need an espresso.
Oh, espresso?
Okay. Okay.
How about basic outerwear, huh?
Like shoes?
Hmm?
That little jog of yours
is all over T.V.
Doris has called me, like, five times.
Publicists live for this stuff, Sam.
Record labels do not.
Not to mention everyone's wondering
when you're gonna stop messing around
and deliver these new songs
you owe them.
I'm just, I'm dealing with
some writer's block right now.
Dude, I'm telling you,
you can't keep putting them off.
All right, Sam...
We have a meeting set
with the label...
Hold on one second.
Oh, crap, it's Blake Shelton.
I gotta get this.
Should be fun.
Hey, Blake.
What's up, buddy?
Terrible accident took place
on I-59 this morning.
27-year-old councilman
Mason Belmont of St. Augustine
was driving on his way
to a city meeting
at approximately 6:30 AM
when he was struck by a drunk driver.
That driver is said to be
in critical condition.
Unfortunately Belmont did not survive.
St. Augustine, known by locals
as simply "Saint,"
is holding an open vigil
at their church tomorrow.
This was the third incident this month...
All right, buddy, we'll talk soon.
All right, thank you.
Okay, Liam, as I was saying,
we're gonna get this meeting,
it's gonna be... Where you going?
You're just gonna walk... Okay.
I guess you're just gonna go. Great.
Get some shoes!
A rooftop?
You kidding me right now, Liam?
We're supposed to be on a flight
to Denver in half an hour.
Jeez, look at you, man.
I'm gonna go get you
a clean shirt or something.
Just get in the car.
Now some sad news to report,
the town of St. Augustine is mourning
the loss of one of their own today.
27-year-old Mason Belmont,
who was born and raised in St. Augustine,
was killed on Tuesday in a car crash.
Hey, Pat,
can you turn that up?
...laid to rest this afternoon.
A funeral service will be held
and St. Augustine Community Church.
Mason leaves behind his wife
and two young children.
Hey.
I'll give you a thousand bucks
if you get me out of here right now.
Yes, sir, boss.
Hey, Pat, I think you should go.
And if you wanna keep your job,
I wouldn't tell anyone where I am.
You got it, boss.
All right.
We're late. Remember, when we get inside,
you give Miss Kiera a big hug...
Oh...
Excuse us.
Hey, sis. Is everything okay?
Liam's here.
- What?
- Here's here.
Turn in our Bibles to Psalms 34:18.
"The Lord is close
to the broken-hearted,
and he saves those
who are crushed in spirit."
I wish I had the answers
to help you understand
why Mason was taken from us.
To help me understand.
I think about this church,
during times like this.
Here in this church,
I've baptized most of you,
married most of you,
baptized your children.
We rejoiced in the good times together
and we bonded together
during the hard times.
So, while I wish I had the answers
as to why,
what I can tell you is this...
That it was here, inside this church,
that Mason Belmont
sat every Sunday morning,
with his family,
with that big smile on his face.
How blessed were we to have had
the privilege of experiencing that smile
that Mason bestowed upon us
through the grace of God?
Hey, Jake, could you
take Billy to the car, please?
Just leave him be, Jos.
Josie, come on.
I got you, little one.
Hey, Liam.
Oh, hey, Dad.
Okay.
Ugh.
Morning.
Mornin'.
What time is it?
It's half past 9:00...
you know, AM.
That tastes awful, Dad.
Really?
Well, it tastes pretty good to me.
Mm-mm.
Uh, make sure you
clean your cup out.
You know, with some soap and water.
You still know how to wash dishes,
don't you, Liam?
Right here.
What happened to Mom's rose garden?
I don't know.
I just couldn't keep up with it.
So, I'll be back around 6:00 tonight.
You... you're just
gonna leave right now?
Well, I'll make us some supper
when I get back.
You know, if you're still around.
Well, um,
I'm not sure how long
I'm gonna be here for.
So...
Right.
Do they have Uber here, or...
How... how else am I
supposed to get around, Dad?
I think your old bike
is still in the garage.
Get out of the pool.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
Have you completely lost
your flipping mind?
I mean,
you've pulled a lot of crap on me,
but you've never missed
and entire concert, Liam.
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
That's good, that's good.
Babe, would you get the kids?
I just don't want them to hear this.
Liam, you missed the whole concert.
Okay? That's 20,000 fans,
and me, and Doris, and the label,
all wondering why Liam Page
isn't at the concert
his people paid good money
to see him play at.
I mean, do you have any idea
how much this costs the tour?
I'll pay them back.
Oh, you're gonna pay them back?
You'll pay them back.
Oh, man, you just don't get it,
do you, buddy?
Okay, do you know,
right now,
the whole world is wondering
where Liam Page is.
Yeah. Have you turned on a TV?
Does that prehistoric cell phone
of yours even have Wi-Fi?
I'm in my home town right now.
In Louisiana. My...
My best friend from high school
passed away.
I just went to his funeral.
Liam, I am so sorry, man,
I mean,
- are you all right?
- Yeah, I think so.
Okay, well...
I just want you to know I'm gonna
get everything settled on this end.
All right? I mean,
that was your last concert date
on that tour,
so we'll just set Denver up
after we go to Europe
on the next tour.
It's all gonna be fine.
You just...
you just be with your friends,
and your family.
And Doris? I mean,
Doris is already spinning
some crazy story
about why you missed that concert.
So don't you even
worry about it, all right?
Hey, Sam...
where are my credit cards?
Why?
I mean, I never seen you use
your credit cards by yourself before.
I... I just, I want...
to buy a few things, that's all.
All I have is the cash in my pocket.
Okay, all right.
Yeah, I'll overnight them.
Thanks, Sam.
Oh... can I get a car?
Just text me your address.
Speaking of crazy, there's Doris.
All right, I gotta go, brother.
All right? We'll talk soon.
Bike it is.
$16.47.
All right.
20, and there you go.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you, and have a good day.
We have more in the back.
Excuse me?
More magazines
with your face on them.
Do you want me
to get those for you?
Nah, I'm good. Thanks.
Lydia.
We went to high school together.
Right.
$24.99, please.
So, Lydia,
you don't happen to know
where Josie lives, do you?
No.
Or where she works?
Thanks for shopping at Ed's.
Here you go.
That'll be $8.69, Mrs. Boudreau.
Oh, Judy, could you pop into the back
and get that arrangement
for Ms. LeBlanc for me?
She's gonna come by this afternoon
to pick it up.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
10...
20...
30...
40...
50...
- Hi.
- I'm with a customer.
60.
You know, this is such
a pretty prayer plant, Mrs. Boudreau.
I think you picked out
the best one I have.
Thank you, dear.
It's for Kiera.
That is so thoughtful of you.
I just adore truly thoughtful people.
7...
8.
Thank you, ma'am.
Now, why don't you let me
help you out to your car.
Hey there, Mr. Boudreau!
Hey, Josie!
Let me get that for you.
Thank you.
Now, you all have a nice day.
We sure will, dear.
Idiot.
That was quite a punch
you socked me with yesterday.
That was just a warning shot.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
So, this is where you work?
I own it.
I bought it after Mrs. Quinn passed
five years ago.
Wow.
Yes, Liam,
I actually did something with my life
after you walked out on me.
And, yes,
a lot of people in this town have come
and gone since you were last here.
My mama passed away.
Do you even know about that?
No.
I'm so sorry.
I... I had no idea.
Have you noticed
that in the past eight years
no one, and I mean no one,
in this little town of ours
has ever spoken to the press
about you
or your life here, ever?
Have you also noticed that no one's
taken a picture of you,
posted it on Facebook,
Instagram, nothing?
And why do you
suppose that is, Liam?
'Cause I walked out on you.
Liam, it's because
you left us all that day.
The entire town.
No one's spoken about
what you did here because...
because we each other's backs
here in Saint.
We're a family.
We're loyal.
But you don't belong here
anymore, Liam.
Please, just leave.
Hey, Mama!
Hi, sweet pea!
Oh, my. Um...
How was your day at school?
You know, the usual. Nothing special.
Hello, Liam.
Laura.
You know what?
Laura's gonna take y'all out
for some cupcakes
at the diner, my treat.
Actually, it's on me.
Let's get going, okay?
I'm just gonna have some soup,
no cupcakes.
I don't want to spoil my dinner.
That sounds nice.
Come on guys, let's go.
Hey! I know you.
You were outside the church yesterday.
You're that country star my mama
listens to sometimes.
I mean, I just sometimes
have the radio on...
Sometimes.
Not really my cup of tea, no offense.
None taken.
I'm a...
I'm a friend of your mom's.
- Liam.
- Billy.
Billy?
Wow.
That's a...
That's a really pretty name.
Okay, sweet pea,
why don't you get going with Laura, okay?
- And I will come up and meet you...
- Just one little minute.
How old are you, Billy?
I'm... I'm really small for my age,
and I'm losing my baby teeth
much later
than everyone else at my age.
I mean, they don't even have
the tiniest little wiggle yet.
But I'm seven.
Okay! Cupcake time, let's go.
Bye, Mama! Nice to meet you, Liam!
Bye, sweet pea!
Um, hey...
Seven, huh?
Well, I guess that conversation
I've played out a million times in my head
is actually about to really happen, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think it is.
I'm gonna need a beer for this one.
I didn't find out that
I was pregnant
until a couple weeks
after our wedding day.
What was supposed to be
our wedding day.
I was so angry and humiliated
after you just walked out on me
and yet,
somehow,
I mustered up all
of the strength I had left...
I called to tell you I was pregnant.
Of course, it went straight
to your voicemail.
I left you some long message
begging you to call me back.
And then I promised myself
that if you didn't have the decency
to call me back
to find out what was so important
that I had to tell you...
I was never gonna contact you again.
Because Billy and I,
we deserve better.
You named her after my mom, Josie.
I did that for your dad, Liam.
She loves him so much.
We all do.
Hey, sis?
What are you doing here, Liam?
Haven't you put her through enough
for one lifetime?
Good to see you, too, Jake.
You know what?
Liam was just leaving, actually.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- I was... I was just leaving?
- Mm-hmm.
All right.
- Why didn't you tell me, Dad?
- Tell you what?
That I had a daughter!
Why didn't you tell me about Billy?
I did tell you.
When? What are you talking about?
We haven't even spoken since I left.
Yeah, exactly.
I went to your, uh,
your first concert there in Seattle.
You wouldn't return my calls,
so I, uh,
had to track you down
like some kind of fan.
Find out where you were performing.
- You were... you were at that show?
- Yup.
I even went backstage to see you after.
Had to plead
with one of the security guards
to let me in to see my own son.
And there... there you were.
You were so out of your mind
on God knows what.
I honestly thought I'd stumbled
into the wrong room.
But even after that,
I still tried to tell you about Billy.
That you had this amazing
daughter on the way.
I don't remember any of that.
Yeah, you don't?
Why don't I refresh your memory?
You told me to leave
and never come back,
although in much more
colorful language.
So what was I supposed to do, Liam?
You were... you were legally an adult.
I couldn't force you
to come home with me.
I was really messed up then, Dad.
Yeah, well, you really seem to have it
all together now, son.
So good for you.
You know what?
I just... I don't get it, Liam.
You were such a good kid,
you were a great son,
You were...
you were great to your friends,
and you were so in love with Josie.
What happened to you, Liam?
What happened?
I don't know.
Well, that guy I saw
in Seattle that night,
I knew that Billy and Josie
were just better off without him.
So, yeah...
Yeah, shame on me.
Good morning, everyone.
Um... well, you know,
It's been a rough time
here in Saint.
It's been a rough few weeks,
and, uh, it's got me
thinking a lot about,
about mercy,
and forgiveness.
You know, scripture says,
"Forgiveness... for in love,
in all love,
we must have the capacity to forgive."
You know, to forgive, it sounds so...
easy, in theory, doesn't it?
And yet it remains so...
so profoundly difficult to achieve.
Trust me, I know.
You know, here inside this church,
we've always practiced forgiveness,
haven't we?
So, with that in mind,
let's try today to...
forgive those that have hurt us,
and to move forward.
And if we can truly forgive,
then we can truly be set free.
Let us pray.
Liam?
I'm glad you're here.
Come on, stick around.
Pastor Page.
You remember Ms. Johnson?
Liam!
Thank you so much for coming.
Good to see you.
- Hey.
- Thank you so much.
See you at fellowship next weekend.
Thank you.
Hey, um, I'm so sorry.
Come here.
Let's go out this way.
April 9th. One saved message.
Hi, Liam.
It's me, Josie.
Dad?
Sweet.
Hi.
Hey.
I'd like to buy some flowers.
For Kiera.
Okay.
Hydrangeas are her favorite.
All right. Perfect.
I'll get... I'll get 24.
24?
Yes...
please.
Okay.
This is 12. Grab that.
Perfect.
Mm-hmm.
That will be $187.51.
Here. I got my own credit card.
Congratulations.
I wanna see Billy.
Sign here, please.
Look, don't ignore me.
I... I know that I haven't been a great...
anything, all right?
But I wanna get to know her.
I'm not gonna cause any trouble,
it can all be on your terms,
but she's my daughter too, Josie,
whether you like it or not.
Can I have a little time
to think about it?
Yeah.
Of course you can.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Here.
Got a, uh...
You got a pen for me to sign?
You sign it with your finger, Liam.
Yeah, I knew that.
You need help with those?
No, I got 'em.
Eight is 32. I always try
to remember that one.
That's a really good one.
Do you want me to cut you a piece?
- Ready?
- Cheers!
Mmm!
Great, huh?
Mm-hmm.
So, sweetie, there is...
There's actually something
I want to talk to you about.
It's about your daddy.
I thought you never wanted
to talk about him.
I did not.
But that is not fair to you.
You have a right to know your father.
But that only is if you want to.
Because if you don't, that's okay, too.
I don't know, he seemed nice to me.
The guy from outside the church
and the flower shop, right?
You two weren't exactly subtle,
if you know what I mean.
Um...
How did you g...
Okay, um...
Yes.
Now, sweet pea, we met
when we were very, very young,
But it is important that you know
that he did not abandon you.
Okay?
He didn't even know that I was pregnant.
Yeah, he looked pretty shocked
when he saw me.
We should invite him over for dinner.
Might help him process the news.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
You amaze me, child.
Unh-uh! That's my blackberry!
Don't you dare eat that, Billy.
Billy!
- Okay, Maria?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Hey, try Liam.
- Of course, ma'am.
Please. Oh, and you know what?
Uh, hold that for a second.
Uh, I want a Cobb salad.
Uh, just, I want it with no chicken,
no tomato, no cheese, no corn.
You know, I'll call it in.
I'll call it in, because the last time
you messed it up,
and you... you got me something
with bananas.
- Yeah, hello?
- Liam!
It's late! Wake up.
Yeah, I am awake.
Who is this?
Hello, it's...
it's Doris Grossnickle-Heinz,
Your favorite lifeline.
- Oh, hey, Doris.
- Hey.
So guess where I have the paparazzi
thinking you are right now?
Uh...
somewhere in the Caribbean, right?
Yes! St. Barts at a rehab for exhaustion.
They are on a wild goose chase
as we speak.
- Great.
- So, listen, those Pap smears
can only run around that tiny little
island for so long without figuring out,
even in their tiny brains,
that you are not there.
So, "L" I am, when am I
gonna tell the public
that you are out of that
sexy little rehab,
because your fans
are chomping at the bit right now.
I'm in my hometown right now, Doris.
An old friend of mine passed away.
Oh.
Oh, that's terrible.
Uh... I'm so sorry, Liam.
But listen to me,
funerals are much better
than rehab for playing
the sympathy card,
so what I want you to do,
is take as many selfies as you can
of yourself in the shower,
shirtless, bottomless, I don't care.
In the coffin, by the coffin,
hugging the corpse.
It doesn't...
just get these pictures in to me,
and I will get you
the cover of People.
Yeah, good bye, Doris.
Liam?
Did he just hang up on me?
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
It's not good.
Oh...
Hello?
Uh, I need to buy something, Sam,
on the Internet.
- You drunk?
- No, I have not been drinking.
Say, if I wanted to buy, uh,
an espresso machine.
How would I...
how would I go about that, man?
Okay, you Google it, you click "buy."
Oh, so it's that easy?
Okay, all right,
say if I wanted to buy, uh,
some... some jewelry,
or a... a teddy bear.
How would I do that?
Okay, what the heck's
going on down there, Liam?
I mean, you said you were gonna
be there for a few days, and...
Yeah, uh...
I think I might...
I might be staying
for a little longer.
Okay, great. So, how long
we talking about?
Turns out, uh,
I have a daughter.
What? Shoot, Liam!
With a groupie?
My ex-fiance from a long time ago.
She's seven.
And her name's Billy.
Sam? You alive?
Yeah, no, yeah, I'm...
I mean, wow.
Liam Page...
is a dad.
You think I'm gonna be terrible at it?
- Yah!
- No, no, no, no, no.
I think you'll be great.
I remember these plates.
Your mom
used to use them all the time.
You knew my mom's mom?
Yeah, I did. I, uh...
I used to come over here for dinner
all the time growing up.
He did, sweetie.
Back when this was my mama's house,
Uncle Jake and I were growing up.
Like the bear?
It's very big.
I mean, you like teddy bears, right?
Yeah, when I was four.
Billy! Manners, please.
Thank you, Liam.
You don't mind me
calling you Liam, do you?
Since I don't know you well enough
to call you "Dad."
Billy Ann! What's gotten into you?
What? It's the truth.
I said I wanted to meet him,
but I never said I'd be easy on him.
She's got a point.
Yeah, "Liam" is fine.
"Liam" is fine, Billy.
Open your present, Mama.
I don't know what to say.
May I be excused?
Um, of course you can, sweet pea.
Hey, Liam,
you wanna see my pet rabbit?
That sounds... that sounds like fun.
You know what?
I'll come with you, okay?
Mama, I'm all right.
You're not gonna kill me
or anything, are you?
Billy Ann, that's enough!
I'm just joking.
Come on.
You're not seriously thinking about
letting that guy
back in your life, are you?
Hello!
Yes, you are so cute.
You want some water?
Here she is.
Yeah.
So, are you gonna
take her out of her cage?
No way!
She might bite me
or scratch my eyes out.
Well...
You mind if... if I take her out?
Okay.
But if she bites you,
you only have yourself to blame.
Okay.
Are you sure
you don't want to pet her?
I'm sure.
She's very soft.
So my mama played me
some more of your songs.
Oh, yeah?
They're better than average, I thought.
Thanks.
So I guess we should get to know
each other or something?
Yeah.
I'd like that.
Why don't you pick me up
after school tomorrow?
I would love that...
Billy.
That was terrible.
I was terrible. I mean,
I don't know how to do kids.
She hated that teddy bear,
just like you hated that necklace.
Liam...
Billy doesn't
need you to buy her things.
And I don't need you
to buy me anything either.
I can't accept this.
She's got your smile, you know.
Got your laugh, too.
You don't remember my laugh.
I can't do that part with you, Liam.
- Good night.
- No, no, no! Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, she...
She asked me if I... if I could
pick her up from school tomorrow.
Liam...
This is moving way too fast.
You're gone for eight years,
and now you want to pick up
my daughter from school?
Our daughter!
I can't...
I have no right to ask for much
here at all.
I know that.
But I'm here now.
And I want to be here, Josie.
I want to get to know Billy.
Please, just...
just give me
the opportunity to do that.
- I'll beg.
- Okay.
Want me to beg?
I'll beg for you.
- I'll beg for you.
- Liam, stop. Get up.
Fine. Tomorrow...
meet me at 3:00 at the old benches.
We can pick her up together.
Thank you.
Do not be late.
I won't... I won't be late.
I promise.
What time?
What time was it again?
Liam...
I know what time it is.
Well, fancy meeting you here.
Mm-hmm.
Can I help you with that?
Yup.
What is this?
It's a car seat.
You know, for a child
to ride in a car.
Never heard of it.
Oh, my God. Maybe this wasn't
such a good idea.
I know what a car seat is.
Come on, give me a little credit.
Okay, so she's gonna be
coming out of these doors right here.
Wow. Same doors
we used to come out of.
Oh...
- Aw, man.
- Need to get that?
No. No, it's my publicist.
Is that the same phone
you've had since high school?
Uh...
I don't... I don't think so, no.
- I remember it.
- Uh...
I...
No, it's... I don't think it is.
It has an antenna, Liam.
I mean, I just...
I like the phone, okay?
Okay.
- Oh...
- Ooh.
Oh, it's Kiera.
I have to take this. I'm sorry.
Hey.
Oh, no, no, no.
Sweetie, don't cry.
You know what, I'm at Wilmington,
but I can be there in ten minutes.
Is that okay?
I'm gonna call you
from the car, Kiera.
I'll be right there.
She's having a really rough time.
Uh...
So, you're going?
You're going right now.
Yeah. I mean, unless you don't think
you can handle this alone.
I'm... I'll just take her in the car...
Okay, I'm gonna call Laura.
She's picking up her kids anyway.
- It's no problem for her to...
- No, no, no, no.
I'm sorry. Look, I, uh...
My dad's house is, like,
two minutes from here.
I think I'll be... I'll be all right.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
Okay, um...
Billy knows
how to put that in the car.
Okay, that's lucky.
So just pay attention
to what she says.
Um... you call me the moment
y'all get home.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Tell her I love her!
Oh, man.
Jumping in the deep end, huh?
- Yeah.
- Car seat and all.
- Yup.
- Where's your car?
Uh... right here.
That's your car?
Yeah.
What's wrong with it?
I don't do convertibles.
They're too dangerous.
Come on, it'll be fun, no?
Do you know the stats on surviving
an accident in a convertible?
No, no, I do not.
Well they are low, Liam.
Staggeringly low.
Do you want to know
exactly how low?
You know what? I'm all right.
Um...
What about Grampy's car?
Maybe... do you like his car?
Is his car okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? All right.
Do you know Grampy's...
Do you know his number?
Now?
Yeah, on the count of three.
One, two...
Hold on, hold on. Be careful now.
And... three.
Smells good, doesn't it?
- Can I stir?
- Yeah.
You're gonna ruin your dinner
with that, you know.
Well, sometimes...
you just gotta let go,
take a walk on the wild side.
Trust that everything's gonna be okay.
Is that chocolate chocolate chip?
Mm-hmm.
I mean, that's the only flavor
that matters.
You want some?
It's pretty good.
Hmm?
Grampy, is it okay?
Um... yeah. Half a scoop.
All right? Don't ruin your supper.
You wanna do it? Okay.
There we go. All right. Now we're living.
Yeah, look at that, that's a mountain.
Wow, okay.
All right, one big, big bite.
Who can take the biggest bite?
One, two, three...
Whoa!
That's a big bite.
Uh-oh.
Guess what, brain freeze?
- Brain freeze! Brian freeze!
- No!
Maybe this wasn't
such a good idea after all.
Yeah.
One sec.
- What?
- It's gonna ruin her supper!
You should have seen her face, Dad.
You should see all this gumbo.
Is this yours?
I found it in Grampy's closet
a while back.
Yeah. Wow.
I have not seen you
for a long time.
How do you come up
with songs to play?
Well, truth is,
I have not been very good at it lately.
But don't tell anyone.
Well, just start playing.
See what happens.
Okay, uh, all right,
smarty-pants.
Uh... what do you want me
to write a song about?
Something about...
Right now, here with us.
Okay.
Um...
Right now...
Here with us...
Uh...
Let's... let's just start
with the melody,
shall we?
That's nice.
I like that.
Who taught you to play
the guitar like that?
Uh, well, my mom.
My mama did,
when I was a little older
than you, actually.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Uh, you all right there?
Yeah, grab that towel there.
- Get this outside.
- It is pretty heavy!
What do you got in there,
some bricks?
A lot of gumbo.
Watch out, it's hot! It's hot. It's hot.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, it's hot.
- Smells pretty good, Dad.
- That's a lot of gumbo.
What did you put in there?
Billy?
You play the guitar?
Nope.
No?
So how do you explain
what you're doing right there?
By watching what you just did.
So, you...
you didn't learn at school, or...
Nope, we don't have that at school.
Wow, uh...
Billy?
Yes?
How would you like it
if I took you to a shop,
and bought you a guitar
of your very own?
Um, why, yes! Yes!
Yes? All right, then it's a date.
Hey, sweet pea, how'd your day go?
I had the best time with you.
Thank you so much, Liam.
Uh, thank you.
Uh, me, too.
I'll see you tomorrow
for guitar shoppin'.
Yeah.
So guitar shopping?
Did you know that Billy
plays the guitar?
- Billy?
- Yeah.
She just picked it up
and started playing.
It was like it was pouring out of her
like she's been playing
her whole life!
- Billy can play the guitar?
- Yes.
That's crazy.
I'm sorry, I told her
I was gonna get her a guitar.
I mean, is it okay if we go
guitar shopping tomorrow,
after school?
You should come with us
until you're comfortable
with me and Billy spending
time together, obviously.
So, you, me, and Billy?
Yeah.
Nothing's gonna happen
between us, Liam.
I... I never said it was.
- Hey, Josie.
- Yeah.
Is it all right if I pick you up
from work tomorrow?
Okay.
I'll pick you up in my dad's car.
Oh. So she, uh,
she gave you those stats
on convertibles, huh?
Yup!
You know, I am so excited
that you're sleeping over.
Your mom said that you liked
to be wrapped up like a little burrito.
- Yup!
- Yeah?
So am I doing this right?
Almost, hang on.
Uh, you forgot the feetsies
and the side.
Are there more? Okay.
There you go.
- Perfect!
- Perfect, like a little burrito.
- Okay.
- Hey, Liam.
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah.
Sure.
What happened?
I mean, why'd you leave my mama?
Oh... man.
Um, well, the short answer is...
that I was young...
and... dumb.
And that's pretty much
the long answer, too.
All I can tell you...
is that...
this one night,
me and your mom were...
singing in a karaoke bar...
we were just goofing around...
uh, but, as luck would have it,
this record exec
heard me singing,
and he asked me
to record a song.
And then the next thing I know,
it's all over the radio,
and then I'm off on tour, just like that.
Like one big wild tornado.
But why didn't you
take my mama with you?
I... I wish I did,
Billy.
Really, I do.
But I...
I was so young, I just,
I-I didn't know...
I didn't know how to handle
being famous.
I guess I just...
I got lost, and I got lost
for such a long time,
I couldn't find my way back.
But you found your way back now.
You're back, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm back, Billy.
I'm back.
- Hey, Liam?
- Mm-hmm.
Could I...
maybe call you "Dad"?
That...
Yeah, I would love that,
more than anything.
Really.
- Okay.
- Okay, good night.
- Good night.
All right, you gonna go to sleep?
Mm-hmm.
Uh...
Billy just asked
if she could call me "Dad."
Yeah.
That's a lot of responsibility.
Yeah, I know.
It's forever, Liam.
I know.
I'm... ready.
Okay.
I-I, um,
I should probably get inside...
Oh! Oh...
- You okay?
- I'm just a little bit tipsy.
Think maybe you could drive me home?
Nope.
Dad?
I'm gonna drive Josie home.
You know, there is something
I would kind of love to do with you.
Yeah? What's that?
I would love...
to go on a date...
with the Liam Page.
No, come on!
I never got to experience that with you.
You know, we could get all dressed up,
go for a fancy dinner somewhere,
drink tons of champagne.
Watch your fans go nuts.
I'd love to do that with you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Are you ready for that?
Oh, I'm ready.
For a date, that is.
With the Liam Page.
How's Saturday night?
Perfect.
Better call your people,
let them know you're coming out
of that Caribbean rehab.
My publicist is gonna be so thrilled.
Night!
Night.
Oh, my gosh,
he gets on my nerves!
Then he fails
the math test, but...
Hey, Billy.
Hey, Dad!
Hey, girls.
- Bye!
- See you tomorrow.
- Yeah!
- Bye, Liam.
- Bye, guys.
Bye!
What... what's that?
Behind your back, what's that?
- Behind my... What?
- Behind your...
- This...
- What, in that hand?
- I can't see a thing.
- Right here, right here, right here!
Right here! I got it.
You got it, you got it,
you got it, you got it.
You didn't!
I did. You wanna do it?
- Yes!
- Yes?
All right!
Grampy's in his car,
so we're just gonna
have to walk, I think.
Why is my car seat in there, then?
Uh, I don't know.
I put it in there just in case.
But I can pick the car up later.
Come on.
No. I'll take it.
You'll... take the convertible?
Yeah.
What about all the stats
you told me about?
Well, sometimes I gotta let go
and walk on the wild side.
Right, Dad?
Trust that everything's gonna be okay.
You are something else, Billy.
What kind of... what kind of music
you want to listen to?
Well, the only one there is... country!
That's my girl.
Yeah!
Whoo!
Wow. Where did you get this dress?
I borrowed it from Miss Laura.
She wore it at a Mardi Gras ball
down in Baton Rouge.
It's pretty, isn't it?
You're gonna look like
a movie star in it.
Thank you, sweetie.
Can I put it on?
Okay. Just a little, okay?
Mm.
Feels perfect.
- Want me to put a little on you?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Oh...
How'd I get so lucky to get you?
I'll get it!
Excuse me, sir?
Do you have any idea
where you're taking me?
Mr. Page wants
it to be a surprise for you.
Wow!
I've never seen what New Orleans
looks like from up here.
It's quite a view, isn't it?
If you look just over there...
we're gonna land right
on the roof of that hotel.
- Right, Jimmy?
- That's right, Mr. Page.
Wait, we're gonna land on that tiny roof?
Uh, yes, we are.
You okay with that?
I guess so!
Well, hold on, here we go.
Oh, welcome!
Welcome, guys, to the French Quarter.
Cody, you're up.
Great to see you
on Southern soil again, Liam.
You too, Cody.
Uh, it's great to be here.
Yeah. On behalf of everyone watching
on Country Music Live right now,
I think we'd all love to know,
who is the beautiful woman
on your arm?
Uh, this is...
the one.
What's her name?
Uh, that's all I got, guys.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Now,
is it just me,
or did the music just stop
and everyone just walked off
the dance floor?
I think they did.
I still haven't opened my eyes yet.
Wow. Yeah, they did.
Thank you.
For what?
For showing me...
how my life could be
with you in it.
Good night.
Uh, good night.
Go.
This is Sam. Leave it.
Hey, Sam. Give me a call back.
I need to talk to you
about the tour.
That smells amazing, Johnny.
Thank you, Josie.
- Hey.
- Hey, now.
- Hi!
- Hey!
- Oh, hey, hold up!
- Go, go, go, go, go.
- We're all about to sit down and eat.
- We're hungry lions, man.
- Yeah, we're hungry lions!
- All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
you don't eat like that.
- Why?
- You gotta put the blood on.
I don't think it needs too much blood.
Needs some blood.
I'm gonna put some blood on mine.
Smear it around.
And then you gotta
smooth it around like that.
And then you're gonna hold it
in the middle, like this.
Then you're gonna...
eat it like a lion.
Grrrr...
Rawr!
There we go!
We're the kings of the jungle right now.
Well, you're the king,
and I'm the queen.
How was that? Good?
- Delicious.
- Mmm.
- What's up, man?
- Grab a beer, man. Join me.
No, I'm all good. I'm just kind of greasy
from the rigs, you know?
- All right, we'll be out here.
- Billy.
Billy! Hey, Liam!
Do something, man.
She's choking!
It's gonna be okay, Billy. I got you.
- Billy's choking! Get out here!
- Billy!
- Take a breath, sweetheart.
- Billy! Come on, come on!
Come on, baby...
She's not breathing!
Baby, come on!
Come on, baby, breathe!
Come on! Jake, it's not working.
She's not breathing!
- Okay, I've got it.
- Jake, you have to do something!
Okay, I have this, okay!
Calm down!
Come on, baby, breathe!
Come on, you got this.
Stay with me, Billy Ann!
Stay with me!
- A couple more. Come on, let's go.
- Come on, baby, breathe!
Julie, give her 10 CCs
of epi and push it.
Come on, Billy!
Liam, sweetie?
Would you go get your daddy for me?
Liam?
Sweetie, I need you to go get your daddy.
I think he went down the hall.
Go get your daddy for me.
Julie, take him to see his dad.
I don't want him to see this.
Come on, Billy Ann Page.
Come on,
there's still a little more in you.
Not yet... not yet...
Come on, baby, breathe!
Come on, you got this!
Come on, baby. Come on.
Take a breath, okay?
Here comes a big one.
Oh!
You're good. You're good...
Oh. I got you.
- Oh, my God...
- Let's get some water.
Let's have some lemonade, okay?
She's all right, she's all right.
I didn't know
what was happening.
It's all over now.
It's all over.
Now, let's eat, everybody.
Drink some more
lemonade for Mama.
Oh, you scared Mama.
You scared me so bad.
Man...
I didn't know you could
sing like that, Walt.
Well, I only sing in this bar.
And you...
you weren't old enough
to come in here before you left.
You know,
I used to sing in here with your mom.
You used to sing with my mom?
Billy and I used to get quite
the crowd in here.
Man...
But it was you she liked
playing with the most.
She was always so proud of you.
That was really nice tonight, Walt.
Thanks, Fred.
You need a ride?
I'm all right.
All right, son.
Take it easy.
- How you doing, Jake?
- Good, Walt.
- Yourself?
- Good.
I had a feeling you'd be here.
Hey, Freddy, can I get a beer?
You got it.
So, you think you're ready to be a dad...
because you spent a couple weeks
playing house?
You know,
my little niece was choking,
and you just sat there, Liam.
I mean, she could have died
if she'd been alone with you.
Man, you gotta be on 24/7
when you're a parent, Liam.
You think you're equipped...
to keep that little girl alive...
every day?
I ain't gonna forget
all the bad years that Josie had
because of you.
Right? And I was there for her.
I'm the one that got her through them.
Josie finally managed to rebuild her life,
not just for her, but for Billy, too.
Because you and I, we both know
that you're just gonna
find some way to mess it up.
And it will destroy them.
You might have...
everyone else in this town
fooled right now, but...
you ain't fooling me.
I can't believe you smashed your hand
through that bar mirror.
I'm almost done.
You'll be able to play again in no time.
I never want to play again.
Now, don't say that, don't say that.
It's a God-given talent
to be able to play
and sing the way you do.
I don't deserve it.
Let's face it.
Just be honest.
I'm a bad person, Dad.
- Liam...
- Come on, it's okay.
It's true!
We've... we've all forgiven you, son.
You shouldn't have.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I left you.
I'm sorry that I didn't
get in touch with you.
I honestly don't know why I did it.
I know, I know.
The further away I went...
and the longer I was gone...
the more pain I was in at the end.
I'm sorry.
I know you are.
I just didn't know how to get out.
I know.
When your mom died, son...
I was so stuck in my own grief...
I somehow overlooked yours.
I got comforting words
for everyone in this town
during their time of need, but...
I wasn't able to talk
to my own son during his.
That wound...
that terrible wound...
losing your mom the way you did
at such a young age,
I think being famous just fed that pain,
knocked down everything in its path.
So I'm the one who's sorry, Liam.
I'm so, so sorry.
Thank you. Thank you, London.
All right, all right.
Liam! Liam!
Great, great show, man.
- Nice singing there, Stacey.
- Thanks, Sam.
Liam, that was seriously
the best set
I think I've ever seen you perform.
Man, I think these new songs of yours,
they're just...
just crushing it, you know?
Just get me out of here, Sam.
Sorry, man.
Liam, why are you
doing this to yourself?
What?
What the heck happened
when you were home?
She almost died because of me.
Who?
Billy.
I mean, we were...
we were all about to have dinner
in the backyard,
and Billy started choking,
and I just... I froze, man.
I was paralyzed by it.
I'm not a fully formed
human being, Sam.
I'm just not.
Liam,
you froze with Billy
because you love her.
She could have died, Sam.
But she didn't die, Liam.
And look,
we all mess up sometimes, Liam.
But it's what you do
after you mess up that counts.
You show up, you be there.
You know what?
This whole time I managed you,
you ain't been nothing
but a big, fat idiot.
- You know that?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's true.
And I get it, I do.
There are far better men than you
out there, no doubt.
Uh-huh.
But Josie doesn't love them, Liam,
she loves you.
And lucky for her, man,
'cause you love her, too.
- Doris?
- Yeah.
- I need to get off this plane.
- You're what?
I need to get off this plane.
Uh, can you ask the pilot
to stay put, please?
- Of course, I'll let the pilot know.
- No, no, no!
You tell the pilot to go!
To fly away!
You... you know that we
are supposed to leave right now,
so we are going... right now...
into the air!
Can you just ask
the pilot to open the door?
You tell the pilot
that you are locking the doors
and we are taking off!
- I need to get off this plane.
- You are not getting off this plane.
- I'm getting off this plane.
- You are performing in Berlin
in 14 hours!
In 14 hours,
I'm gonna be in Louisiana.
All right!
For the love of God,
do not get off this plane.
April 9th, one saved message.
Hi, Liam. It's me, Josie.
I've called you so many times,
I've lost count.
I still don't know why you left me
on our wedding day.
I don't know if I'll ever find out.
But I really need you to call me back.
If you don't, I promised myself
that I'll never call you again.
I have to find some way
to move on with my life.
But I want you to know...
If I don't ever hear back from you...
I will always love you, Liam.
You will always be the one for me.
And you'll have my heart forever.
Hey, it's Josie. Leave a message.
Uh...
Hey... Josie.
It's me.
It's taken me eight years
to return this message.
I mean, I always wanted to.
But I knew that I needed
to know how to tell you...
why I did what I did.
And I hadn't figured it out...
until now.
You see, my mom was the love
of my life until I met you.
And...
I know we were young,
but the thought of possibly
losing you one day,
the way that I lost her...
I found my heart couldn't take it, so...
I ran...
But I could never move on, Josie.
And that message that you left me,
I did listen to it.
I listened to it every day
for the last eight years.
And then, when I met Billy,
my heartjust burst open.
I thought I wasn't good enough
for you two.
But I'm gonna spend
the rest of my life trying to be.
I'm never leaving Saint again
without you and Billy by my side.
Josie!
You're the one.
You've always been the one.
So you've been carrying around
this old, beat up, duct-taped,
really ugly cell phone
the past eight years
because of me?
Yeah.
And you really
listened to that message
every single day
since I left it there?
Yeah.
And you're not ever leaving
Saint again without Billy or me?
Never.
Then I just wanted to say...
welcome home.
Hey, I'm Jake.
Hi, I'm Doris.
Well, it's nice to meet you, Doris.
You smell good, Jake.
- Yeah!
- Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
- Whoo!
- Go, Billy!
Whoo!
And for once,
you all know my dad.
This is a song we like to call,
"Finally Home."
Hi.